Hello everyone!
This is Alice Yamano and
Yuka Murayama.
Nice to meet you.
This time, I would like to do a chatting make-up with you two.
It's our first time, right, at Miyajima?
Yes, I'm so glad that you let me do your makeup.
It's a little embarrassing.
Yes, we are both still working on the base right now,
In other words, we are only doing the base, so let's do a little makeup.
I'd like to introduce what we used for the base.
First of all, I use two base products as a primer,
Sunscreen?
I use one called Naroche-Posay.
I put it on first.
The white one.
It's famous.
This is COSME DECORTE's primer. It's pink and tones up your skin. It's very good.
Nice, nice. It's like this, the primer. I can use something called "Kanso.
It's a very inexpensive product, but it really doesn't dry out my skin and I can use it even during live performances.
I use this one for live performances, too.
I have dry skin, so the name "Mr. Dry" appeals to me too.
I'm using a concealer.
I'm using a concealer from the "M" line. What's the number? Is it the brightest one? Yes, the brightest one. It's just white.
I think everyone uses foundation Lil Vis, but I use the lightest one, No. 21.
It's the same for everyone. Performance powder and Perfect Diary white color.
I use number 01. It's nice.
Base makeup is completed with this.
The silky type?
Yeah, it goes on smooth.
It's pretty good.
It's good.
Okay, my base makeup.
Foundation.
COSME DECORTE ZEMBER FILLED.
I think the number is C, 11.
I like Decorte.
It's very moisturizing.
It's my favorite base makeup.
It's very reliable.
I use concealer on top of it.
This is Dior Skin Forever
Skin Correct Concealer
It's probably the brightest one I've ever used.
It's good.
It's a concealer.
It's a concealer that hides the concealer.
I put a little highlighter on my nose and high points.
I put a little highlighter on the nose and high points.
Here?
Here and here.
Concealer and
And a little bit more.
It's a little bit of a highlighter today.
It's so good, it's great!
I also use Lilibeth only when I need to fix it!
Cute stickers!
Don't lose them!
Everyone uses stickers!
I put some cute stickers on my uncle's.
This is for fixing.
I use Shu Uemura's Unlimited MOPO loose powder.
It's cute!
It makes it smooth and silky.
That's all.
Base makeup
Totally different eyes
I used totally different eyes.
Interesting.
Shall we do the makeup then?
Yes, let's do it.
Where do we start? I always start with shading.
I always start with shading.
Maybe we're the same.
Really?
You do?
I've been starting with shades lately.
What do you use?
I use Cezanne.
It's number 02.
That's good, that's good.
That's good.
I put it under the chin and on the bridge of the nose.
I'll show you some shades. I'm using Canmake's No. 04.
I've recently started using this and a liquid shade. Sunsculpt Liquid Shade.
Gently.
Brush?
Rosie Roser.
I can't get over it.
How do you do your makeup?
Shading is so important.
It's really important.
When we go to live shows, all the members, they all shade in their spare time, don't they?
Everyone is shaving it off, saying it might not be enough.
It makes me anxious, doesn't it?
I am insecure.
Do you have a nose? Alice...
Well, I really, really pull it straight.
It's important to have a straight nose.
I always use a brush, and if there is a dent here or there, I just pull it straight.
There are a lot of random places, so it's surprisingly easy.
I'll do my best not to make any dents.
I'll try my best not to rub it in.
Alice had a personal color diagnosis?
We all had it done, but what did you think?
I was first in summer as a Burgundy, and second in spring as a Yaybe.
I see. So it was summer and spring.
It was summer and spring.
I don't get it.
How about you, Yuka-chan?
I'm Brubeck's summer and Brubeck's summer.
Winter, right? Second winter. You are a Bourbé. Yes, I was very much a Bourbe.
Flower completion. Ah, completion. It's kylite.
Yes, it's realistic. Realistic. Where do you use it? Always.
Always, down here? Two down here. Two down here. The bottom left is completely gone,
Look there. It's Al-Al, isn't it? Al-al. Too close to the eyes.
A little too close to the face. That's nice.
I'm a little eyebrow. Without eyebrows, my face is a bit.
I feel like it's not tight enough, so I want to draw my eyebrows first.
I use eyeshadow to create and apply the darker part of my eyebrows, so I'm going to introduce eyeshadow with you.
The eyeshadow is a head main in a color called Picnic by the Sunset, number 13 in the Clio Pro Eye Palette.
It's pretty.
I put a little bit of color here, a little bit more here, and a little bit of feeling here.
I use a powder that I mix like I'm going to put it in.
It's a really pretty color.
It's so pretty.
I use only this corner,
I have to use all the corners.
I'm going to apply it.
Take a brush like this, and paint like this.
The more you remove it, the thicker it gets,
The more you remove the brush, the thicker the eyebrows will be.
Eyebrows.
It looks like the bridge of the nose is done.
Next?
Eyebrows.
Eyebrows, really.
I haven't quite figured out how to draw them yet, and I've been doing it in a haphazard way.
Eyebrows are difficult, aren't they?
They are really difficult.
My eyebrows are really difficult for me.
Eyebrows change the impression of your face.
Yeah.
People often say that.
But I think it's okay because it's kind of hidden.
I sometimes have them.
Yes, I do. It's hidden by the bangs.
It's difficult, isn't it?
It's difficult.
Someday, you know, when I lift my bangs.
It will be obvious.
Will they know?
I don't think so.
After applying the powder, I'm going to apply my eyebrow mascara next.
The eyebrow mascara is Kiss Me Heavy Rotation Coloring Eyebrow #03.
It looks a little more used up.
Do you have any particular makeup obsessions with Alice?
I've been showing off my eyelashes lately.
They're always so beautiful.
What about you, Yuka?
I do eyelashes and tear troughs.
I always put a lot of effort into my tear ducts.
That's right, that's right.
It's true, I have an image of full tear troughs.
Really?
I draw a lot of shadows.
People might think I'm adding so much to my tear ducts.
I may be drawing a little air, but I'm sticking to my guns.
I like the zero on the chart.
I'm in pink.
I'm going to continue with the eyebrows.
I've got a lot of these...
This is the Micro-Brow Pencil No. 451 from Rebellon. It's a very fine pencil.
I also use it on my eyebrows.
Parallel eyes? I'd like to learn how to wear it, you know, like there are guidelines, like where the eyebrow peak should be.
I know, but it's difficult.
Now that I'm done with the eyebrows, I'd like to start on the eyeshadow.
I'm going to use the same eye shadows as well, this one by Krio and this one by Momoka, a birthday present from her.
I got this as a birthday present from Momoka.
I'm going to use a slightly pinkish, more pink color from Wake Makeup.
I saw Momoka using it and thought it was nice.
I told her I liked it, and she gave it to me as a present, and here's another one!
It's a bluish-dusky pinkish color from Excel.
I wonder what color it is?
I mix these two and apply both the top and bottom.
I also have another one.
This one is also from Jill Stuart.
Pretty shimmery.
I'm using something like Unicorn Utopia.
So cute!
It's kind of super cute.
It's true. It's cute.
The colors are so pretty like this. You could use all the colors in this palette.
I'm always looking forward to seeing who I'll use. I'll use this second pink from the right today.
That's nice.
So you're a hands-on type. How long does it usually take you to do makeup, Alisa?
About an hour? It takes me about an hour.
It takes me an hour, too. But when you start focusing on your eyelashes, doesn't it take a long time?
Eyelashes take forever, don't they?
Here, I draw the tear troughs.
Tear troughs
Makeup is so difficult, isn't it?
I'm still working on it.
Was it during the audition? Alice's makeup was really heavy, and she's so beautiful from the start, but I have the impression that it's totally different from now.
I was in the third grade at the time, but I don't think I was expecting it.
Alice looked mature. She wore heavy make-up and her lips were bright red.
When you're freshly made up, you start with the lips.
If the lip color is red, the redder the color, the more blood color, so it goes on and on.
The bottom line. It's in.
I'm looking forward to seeing it finished.
I like to put a lot of makeup on the lower eyelid.
I like to put a lot of make-up on the lower eyelid, and not at all on the upper one.
That's my point.
That kind of thing is really popular these days, isn't it?
You apply the upper eyelid in the front, but you apply the center of gravity on the bottom.
I often do that.
I apply it to the tear ducts and the edge of the lashes.
A little bit of light pink
Dark light pink.
This is spunk?
This is spunk.
Which one? Which one is it?
I mixed the colors diagonally.
These are tear troughs, but they're Korean, so I can't read them.
Do you think it shows up?
It's a little bit like a tear duct concealer.
It's good.
You apply it on the upper lid.
I'm going to layer it. Love.
On the top.
It depends on the mood of the day, but I use this area.
Around here.
Upper eyelid
It's a little below the width of the double fold.
I'm going to write tear troughs again.
I'm using a slightly pinkish-beige color.
I'm using a pink-beige kind of color. I'm going to layer it.
I'm going to write on the tear troughs too.
For the tear ducts, I'm using One More Tensil R Spot Highlight Rose #03.
Wee Idol.
I'm using
I'm going to put this on my tear ducts.
It's a highlighter, but for the tear ducts.
It's kind of shimmery, a little bit.
It's got lame in it.
It's got a little bit of lame in it.
I'm going to apply it to the high part of the tear ducts.
I'm going to apply it.
I see.
Here's what I like to do.
Before this dries.
It's a little bit of a feeling thing.
Before it dries, I'm going to put some lame on it.
I'm going to put it on.
I'm going to put it on. I see!
I feel like it won't come off.
I mix the highlighter with the white part here, the white part here, the white part here, and the white part here... anyway, I mix them according to my mood.
I mix a lot of different things. It depends on the day, but today I want to mix this area because I want to make my eyes look a little more glamorous and sparkling.
Before it dries! Before it dries!
Race against time! Race against time!
Today's makeup is lighter than the live makeup, so maybe I'll go natural.
I'm going for a natural look.
I'm going to use a line for the tear ducts.
I'm using something like Heroine Make 01 Kajiliner.
Heroine Makeup's shadow drawer.
Yes, I drew it.
I want to draw a guideline for the eyeliner in the black area above
Eyeliner
Eyeliner.
Recently, I've been into drawing a little bit of a pouty eye, and I'm not very good at it yet, but I've been looking down a little bit, and I think it's somewhere around this area.
Eyeliner is difficult. It's difficult because it gives a different impression.
I'm going to fill in the triangle with this brown color.
I'm going to fill in the triangle with this brown.
I use a mixture of here and here.
I'll apply blush.
I'm using blush by EXCEL.
Cheek Color Peach.
Like peach & peach.
I think it's peach & peach.
It's a gradation.
It's so pretty.
I use the top one.
I use this and Sezanne's Natural Blush N01 depending on the day.
It's my mood.
Separate?
I see.
I always make an L like this.
I always make an L like this so that it fits inside.
Oh! You have twin points.
That's great.
I don't know if this is really the right place to put the blush.
I don't know if this is really the right position.
But the position I'm into these days is
I like to put it on the inside of my face when I do an L like this.
Wow! I see.
I don't know what the right answer is, but if you think it's right, then yes, it's okay.
If you think it's good, it's good.
The bottom right of the Anus eyeshadow palette.
The bottom right is better.
I put the dark brown on the corner of my eyes.
Oh, the bottom.
The brown color makes your eyes look bigger.
It makes them look bigger.
I'd like to apply lame.
I'm going to apply lame. I'm going to use this lame.
I take this with my finger and put it on the top of the dark eye.
Does it look good? It's good? It's pretty sparkly.
When I put the lame on, it makes my eyes look more open. It makes them look more open.
The lame on the tear ducts...
The lame for tear troughs was recommended by the staff at Marie Quent.
The lame for the tear ducts.
It's cute!
It's pretty glittery.
I'm using it in a good way.
It's also used on the lower eyelid.
Cute. The packaging is cute.
I'm going to use it as a blush.
Eyes are almost done.
So fast!
Basic #06
I'm using color #06.
This cute little strawberry!
So cute!
It's pink.
I've borrowed it too.
Yes, people often ask me to borrow it.
Alice's blush looks great at live performances.
The color is so cute.
Yes, it is.
Everyone says I can borrow Alice's blush.
They're all borrowing it.
I mix and match all of these.
I'm using an eyelash curler.
It's from SHISEIDO.
Wow, it's from SHISEIDO!
Here's a brush.
Korin
Your English is so difficult.
Here it is.
It's a brush for eyeshadow and other things.
and a big one.
And a big one.
It's perfect for carrying around.
That's nice.
Very convenient.
And on top of the blush.
I'll put on the top pink.
I put the pink one on top. From the top.
I also put blush on the chin and the nose. I do have an image of Alice with a nose.
It's cute, isn't it?
Eyelashes are up.
I also put on Elegance's Curl Lash Fexor mascara primer.
I've been using Elegance's Curl Lash Fexor mascara primer for a long time.
I've been using it ever since I joined Niaju.
Wow, that's great!
Yeah, when I run out, I'll just get this one.
I hear it's good.
It's amazing!
It's really, really, really great.
I'm interested.
I use Milk Touch AD Long & Curl Mascara.
I use Milk Touch mascara so that it extends.
It's so long!
I'm going to go crazy with it.
You have to focus on the mascara.
I think I'm going to do mascara too.
I've been using...
Majolica Majolica
Lash Bone Black Fiber-In
Lash primer.
I'm using it.
Like this.
And here's the black mascara
Lash Exposure Funder
I use Dolly Curl.
It's pitch black.
Hot mascara
I don't remember the name of this one.
If you look up red, it comes up right away.
If it's another hot muffler, I think it's this one.
Leave it in the studio while I put it in.
While I'm putting it in, I'll go to the studio.
Focus.
It's kind of a speedy game.
I use this again for the tear troughs.
It's thin, so I write it on the tear troughs in a "c" shape.
I write it in the shape of the letter "C" on the tear troughs.
I let it dry a little bit.
I dry it with a mirror.
Then, I finally use the photo bureaus.
Heroine Make Prime Liquid Eyeliner
Rich Keep #03.
Do you have #03?
Yes, I do.
I've been using this one for a long time. I'm on my third bottle.
I put this where I drew the guideline earlier.
With eyeshadow.
I draw a line where I drew the guideline.
That's great.
You don't inline?
No, I don't.
When I look up, I lose the double width.
I don't want to make the upper eyelid look as wide as possible.
I want to make it look as wide as possible.
I see.
I do that a lot.
I highlight.
Yes, I do.
Your eyelashes are elaborate.
What are you doing?
They're so beautiful.
It's like a pineapple.
I do eyelashes.
I see.
That's why you're not here today.
Normally...
This is from Heroine Makeup, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a brower.
It's good. It's good.
I use it when I don't have enough curl.
Highlighter
Pearl Glow Highlighter No. 01 by Sezanne.
I use this one.
Yes, I use it.
Here on the nose and eyes?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Here.
It's pretty shiny.
It's fine for live performances.
But for everyday use, I apply it sparingly.
And the tip of the nose.
Nose tip azure.
Izzy.
I think I'll put on lipstick.
I'm going to put lipstick on.
I'm going to do the lip rim.
I'm using Lee Idol's Lip Shape Pink.
Number 01.
No. 01 pink.
I'm going to apply it right here where it looks like an "M".
Make the top bigger.
Use lame.
Yes, ma'am.
Hoomie.
Mm-hmm.
Single lamé shadow in Melinda Beige.
I'm gonna apply this to the tear ducts.
It looks like this.
It's so, so beautiful.
So beautiful.
I'm using Laka Fruity Glam Tint No. 106 Juicy on my lips.
It's almost gone.
Almost gone.
I'm using it.
And
It's a good line.
It's Cammake's creamy touch liner No. 02.
I opened it.
This one's brown?
Yes.
I don't know how to say it.
Here.
I'm drawing here.
Between the lashes?
Yes.
The lip.
Yes, sir.
Now, let's do the eyeliner.
This is Heroine Makeup eyeliner, number 02.
I'm using a dark brownish-black kind of color.
I think all the members use this.
They use it.
Let's take a look.
I'm going to apply gloss.
It's Dior Addict Lip Glow Oil No. 001 Pink.
Aimi gave me this as a birthday present.
I've been using it for a long time now.
It's so good!
It's a gloss tayl
It says "oil" on the label.
It's an oil, so it's amazing!
It moisturizes afterwards.
It moisturizes and keeps the skin moist.
It's so good!
I love it.
It looks different in natural light.
It changes.
I'll add some lame.
I'm going to add some more lamé, and I got this from another lamprey, Zeke's Glitter.
I don't know, I've never seen this before, but it's a big lamé.
I'm not sure of the number, but it's a big lamé and I put it on the highest part of my tear ducts.
I put a little bit of this on the highest part of my tear ducts.
I think it makes the tear troughs look bigger and fuller than white ones.
It makes them look fuller.
I'm painting the tear ducts with pink. I've learned.
I've learned to use a long iron.
I've been using this a lot lately.
I've just learned that this is for eyebrows.
It's for eyebrows, but I use it for tear troughs.
I see.
Shadows.
At first, I draw a soft shadow with eye shadow.
Then I use a thin liquid pencil to make it stand out even more.
That's amazing.
I'm really into it.
I'm going to run with the triangles.
Go ahead, take your time.
Oh, color contacts.
Colored contacts.
I use Topaz Date Topaz color contacts.
Topaz, me too. I brought some Topaz today. I'm throwing them out.
It's Topaz Glow Brown, by Fingerlings. Fingerlings, by Fingerlings. I love it.
It's really good. It's really good. It doesn't dry out my eyes.
It's really natural. It's really natural.
It's really maturational. It's very glitchy.
It's not easy to pull out. It's surprisingly okay.
I'd rather use my hands than tweezers, because I have the best feel for it.
It's cute, isn't it? I'm curious. I'm curious.
It's the same kind of Perfect Diary highlighter as the powder!
It's so cute!
It's so sparkly!
Let's open it up.
Open it up.
It's so cute!
It's so cute.
It's pure white, and it's a star.
It's really... very detailed.
Yes, it is.
It's cute.
I use it all the time.
As a highlight.
Highlight.
On the nose.
And here on the eyes.
It's cut, it's cut, it's cut.
I haven't put it on yet, but I'm going to put it here.
I'd love it if you guys could copy it.
And I'll finish with the lips.
The lipstick is Dewby Film No. 10 in Shupi Shupi
and Glass Flamper No. 03.
The color of the gloss is a bit purplish.
It's a little bit purplish.
I think the color is not bluish, so it's easy to use at all.
Finished! I'm done too!
Okay, I've finished my makeup. What do you think?
I hope it was helpful to you. I'm very happy.
If you like it, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to my channel.
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
That's all for now, this is Nearly Kaoru.
Bye bye!